american-classifieds.net 2019-06-26

# American Classifieds

At american-classifieds.net (the Site) we understand and respect your concerns about privacy. We have created this Privacy Policy to provide you with notice of what information we may collect, how such information may be used or shared with third parties, and how such information relates to the operation of the Site. You are responsible for checking this page periodically for changes and updates to the Privacy Policy. Your use of the Site following any posted changes to the Privacy Policy will be deemed an acceptance of such changes. 

**Cookies**

We may use cookies to store information. The intent of cookies is to identify your computer preferences and searching patterns. We will not disclose the information collected with cookies to third parties except as required by a valid legal process. 

Most internet browsers are set up to accept cookies. You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. 

**Third-Party Advertising Companies**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. 

[Read here how Google uses data when you use their partners' sites or apps](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/partners/). 

**What Information Do We Collect?**

We do not secretly collect information about you (such as your name, email address, etc.) except when you specifically and knowingly provide such information during the ad submission or update process, or by submitting any form on our website. This information may be used to contact you, if needed, with alerts, notices, or confirmations regarding your submission. We may note and save information such as time of day, browser type, browser language, and IP address with each query. That information is used to verify our records and to provide more relevant services to users.

The public will see any information that you provide when you submit a listing. Please do not post any personal information that you expect to keep private. 

**Data We Store**

All postings, web logs and other records may be stored in our database or archived elsewhere. Although we make good faith efforts to store the information in a secure operating environment that is not available to the public, we cannot guarantee complete security. 

**Links to Other Sites**

The sites displayed as search results or linked to by the Site are developed by people over whom we have no control. These other sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data, or solicit personal information. It is important that you preview their Privacy Policy and remove any cookies from your computer if you have any concerns.
